(Sheldon:)It'd be swell
if they had a train.
(Sheldon:)Thank you, Penny.
(Penny:)No problem.
(Penny:)So, Leonard,
(Penny:)I think it's interesting
you didn't call your girlfriend
(Penny:)to come get you.
(Leonard:)Uh, I kind of
told her I was working.
(Penny:)So you lied to her.
(Penny:)Also interesting.
(Leonard:)Yeah, she doesn't really
understand
(Leonard:)the whole Warcraft
adventure-role-playing thing.
(Penny:)Well, doesn't matter if she gets
it, as long as she's pretty.
(Howard:)This one's funny,
Leonard.
(Howard:)How come you couldn't
make it work with her?
(Penny:)So did you at least get
Sheldon's fake stuff back?
(Sheldon:)No. We failed
in our noble quest.
(Penny:)How come?
(Sheldon:)Todd Zarnecki was mean.
(Penny:)All right. Hang on.
(Leonard:)What are you doing?
(Penny:)I'm gonna show you how we
finish a quest in Nebraska.
(Penny:)Oh. Beyonce.